thinkspain.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 2018

The registered owner of the thinkSPAIN.com domain is Think Web Content S.L. (hereafter referred to as “TWC”, “thinkSPAIN”, "us" or "we"), company registration number B-02283380, with registered offices at Calle Thomas Alva Edison 7, 46980 Paterna, Valencia, Spain.

TWC is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and availability of your personal data, and has taken the appropriate technical and organisational security measures to avoid unauthorised access, removal or modification of these details in accordance with Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2016/679.

### Security of your personal data

When you provide personal data via the forms on this website, you always do so with your express consent and in a secure environment since we use SSL encryption for communication between the server and the browser. The webpages that use this data encryption start with https.

We can legally process your data when you expressly consent that we can do so by ticking the I have read and accept the privacy policy checkbox found on the forms on our website, or by any means we put at your disposal that indicates to us your unequivocal consent, e.g. registering as a user. The data will be kept as long as you do not request its removal and for as long as required to meet our legal obligations and responsibilities.

### What we do with the data provided by you

We will store the data you provide, e.g. name, e-mail, telephone number, message, opt-in tick box options, along with associated data, e.g. property ID, and process this data in order to provide the service you need.

We may also send you related information we believe may be of interest, e.g. our weekly thinkSPAIN newsletter, featured properties, property alerts, services offered by third parties. You can easily unsubscribe or change your e-mail communication preferences using the links provided in the e-mails we send you, in the Preferences section of your account if signed in, or by sending an e-mail to data@thinkspain.com from the e-mail address to which your changes relate.

### Who do we share your data with?

The data you provide will not be provided to other third parties unless required by law or legal process, or to be able to fulfil the purpose for which they were provided.

To this end, if the data you provided was done so in order to contact a third party, e.g. the advertiser of a property, job vacancy or business listing, then we will provide this data to the third party so they can contact you directly.

### How to exercise your data protection rights

To exercise your rights, such as your right to access, rectification, deletion, opposition, limitation or portability of your personal data, send your written request to data@thinkspain.com or by ordinary mail to our registered office as detailed above, clearly stating the right you wish to exercise and including the following:

  * Name and surname of the person making the request.
  * Copy of national ID card, passport, residency card or digital signature.
  * Email address used when providing the personal data.
  * Postal address and contact telephone number.

You can withdraw your consent at any time, which will not affect the legality of any data processing carried out prior to its withdrawal.

The right to recourse can be exercised through the Spanish Agency for Data Protection (www.agpd.es).

### Cookies

When you browse the thinkSPAIN website, you provide us with some information on the pages you visit or actions you take, e.g. saving a search. To find out how we use cookies, please see our Cookies Policy.

### Links to other websites

This privacy policy only applies to the data collected on thinkSPAIN. Should you click on a link that takes you to another website, you must take into account that you are leaving our website and should thus read the privacy policy of that website since we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.
